Guide to the Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records, 1942-2005.
Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records, 1942-2005
- Series X. Publicity
  - Slides - textiles lab, equipment, fabrics, no date (Box 5)